Guide to the Railroad Stock Certificate Collection, 1857-1970 AIS.2015.06
ULS Archives Service Center
Railroad Stock Certificate Collection
1857-1970
AIS.2015.06
ULS Archives Service Center
0.5 linear feet
This collection contains 51 stock certificates dating from 1857 to 1970 documenting the history of railroads in western Pennsylvania. Also included are various items such as correspondence, bills of lading, telegrams, valuation of baggage tickets, dividend check, a lease, and employee transit passes for the Pennsylvania Railroad Lines West of Pittsburgh.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Scope and Content Notes
Fifty-one stock certificates dating from 1857 to 1970 documenting the history of railroads in western Pennsylvania. Also included are various items such as correspondence, bills of lading, telegrams, valuation of baggage tickets, dividend check, a lease, and employee transit passes for the Pennsylvania Railroad Lines West of Pittsburgh.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Ken Kobus on June 2015.
Arrangement
Stock certificates are arranged chronologically accordingto railroad division. Additonal manuscript items are arranged by item type and date.
History
Something about history of the railroads is to go here. Will be supplied by Ken Kobus
- Cleveland, Painesville and Ashtabula R. R. Co. Stock Certificate, February 16, 1857 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- New Castle & Beaver Valley R.R. Co. Stock Certificate, April 21, 1876 (Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania Company Stock Certificate, May 25, 1876 (Folder 3)
- Western New York and Pennsylvania Railway Co. Stock Certificate, May 15, 1895 (Folder 4)
- Pittsburgh, Wheeling and Kentucky Railway Co. Stock Certificate, February 1,1907 (Folder 5)
- Pittsburgh, Youngstown and Ashtabula Railway Co. Stock Certificate, September 28, 1938 (Folder 6)
- Ohio Connecting Railway Co. Stock Certificate, April 20, 1953 (Folder 7)
- Cleveland and Pittsburgh Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, January 16,1962 (Folder 8)
- Pennsylvania Company Stock Certificate, August 24,1964 (Folder 9)
- Erie and Pittsburgh Railroad Company Stock Certificate, March 7, 1968 (Folder 10)
- Erie and Pittsburgh Railroad Company Stock Certificate, ca.1968- 1970 (Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Company Stock Certificate, May 15,1969 (Folder 12)
- Pennsylvania Company Sinking Fund Bond, August 25, 1970 (Folder 13)
- Western Pennsylvania Railroad Stock Certificate, April 5,1860 (Folder 14)
- Allegheny Valley Railroad Stock Certificate, September 28, 1866 (Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company Stock Certificate, 1868 (Folder 16)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company Stock Certificate, June 1868 (Folder 17)
- Western Pennsylvania Railroad Company Stock Certificate, April 5, 1860 (Folder 18)
- Pittsburgh, Virginia and Charleston Railway Co. Stock Certificate, May 14, 1890 (Folder 19)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Stock Certificate, April 26, 1913 (Folder 20)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Stock Certificate, February 7, 1917 (Folder 21)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Stock Certificate, August 13, 1951 (Folder 22)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company Stock Certificate, June 5, 1959 (Folder 23)
- Ohio & Pennsylvania R.R. Co. Stock Certificate, October 11, 1853 (Folder 24)
- Steubenville and Indiana Railroad Company Stock Certificate, ca. 1850 (Folder 25)
- Fort Wayne & Chicago Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, March 29, 1860 (Folder 26)
- Ohio & Indiana Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, January 10, 1856 (Folder 27)
- Pittsburgh, Fort Wayne and Chicago Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, March 29, 1860 (Folder 28)
- Pittsburgh, Fort Wayne and Chicago Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, October 3, 1906 (Folder 29)
- Pittsburgh, Fort Wayne and Chicago Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, November 11, 1956 (Folder 30)
- Pittsburgh, Fort Wayne and Chicago Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, ca. 1900 (Folder 31)
- Pittsburgh, Fort Wayne and Chicago Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, ca. 1900 (Folder 32)
- Little Miami Railroad Company Stock Certificate, ca. 1850 (Folder 33)
- Steubenville and Indiana Railroad Company Stock Certificate, June 9, 1856 (Folder 34)
- Grand Rapids and Indiana Railroad Company Stock Certificate, July 21, 1958 (Folder 35)
- Pittsburg and Steubenville Rail Road Company Stock Certificate, March 1, 1859 (Folder 36)
- Holiday's Cove Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, December 4, 1866 (Folder 37)
- Columbus, Chicago and Indiana Central Railway Company Stock Certificate, April 18, 1871 (Folder 38)
- Columbus, Chicago and Indiana Central Railway Company Stock Certificate, November 21, 1881 (Folder 39)
- Chicago, St. Louis and Pittsburgh Railroad Company Stock Certificate, May 15, 1883 (Folder 40)
- Chicago, St. Louis and Pittsburgh Railroad Company Stock Certificate, October 16, 1883 (Folder 41)
- Chartiers Railway Company Stock Certificate, January 27, 1886 (Folder 42)
- Chicago, St. Louis and Pittsburgh Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, May 7, 1889 (Folder 43)
- Pittsburgh, Cincinnati and St. Louis Railway Co. Stock Certificate, June 26, 1889 (Folder 44)
- Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway Company Stock Certificate, January 10, 1898 (Folder 45)
- Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway Company Stock Certificate, March 15, 1910 (Folder 46)
- Columbus and Zenia Railroad Company Stock Certificate, October 29, 1925 (Folder 47)
- Pittsburgh, Youngstown & Ashtabula Railway Company First General Mortgage Bond, May 28, 1924 (Folder 48)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, August 9, 1954 (Folder 49)
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad Co. Stock Certificate, June 6,1966 (Folder 50)
- Pittsburgh & Moon Run Railroad Company Stock Certificate, ca. 1890 (Folder 51)
- test, 2016